Finding Aid for Vice-President for Development (University of Michigan) records, 1948-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Development Office, 1943-1992
  - Audio-Visual Materials
    - VHS Videotapes
      - President's Advisory Group, Planning, 1:30-2:30prn, 6/4/1992 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, Planning, 6/4/1992 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, 12/3/1992 (Box 54)
      - Sharing Best Practices for Major and Planned Giving Officers, Session 1-6, 3/30/2001 (Box 54)
      - "Team Michigan" Kickoff VIS TC Bum, 9/18/I992 (Box 54)
      - Telefund Training Video, 1993 (Box 54)
      - Towards an Inclusive University: Stories from the History of Diversity at the University of Michigan, 1999 (Box 54)
      - Victory Celebration, 9/26/1997 (Box 54)
Related Material
For further information on the history of development programs at the University of Michigan, researchers should see the Michigan Memorial-Phoenix Project records and the University of Michigan Development Council records, both housed at the Bentley Historical Library.